Exercise 10-2, Lax Vowels. The lax vowels are produced in the throat and are
彼此其实非常相似。下面练习一些松元音。记住：
actually quite similar to each other. Let's practice some lax vowels. Remember
有声辅音结尾时，记得把元音拉成双阶梯。
to double the vowel when the word ends in a voiced consonant. One, end, it, un,
earn. Two, bet, bit, book, butt, burn. Three, kept, kid, could, cut, curt. Check,
Chick, Chuck, Church, Five, Debt, Did, Does, Dirt, Six, Fence, Fit, Foot, Fun,
First, Seven, Fell, Fill, Full, Furl, Eight, Get, Guilt, Good, Gut, Girl, Nine,
Help, Hit, Hook, Hut, Hurt, Ten, Held, Hill, Hood, hull, hurl, eleven, gel, jill,
jump, jerk, twelve, ked, kid, cook, cud, curd, thirteen, crest, crypt, crook,
crumb, fourteen, let, little, look, lump, lurk, fifteen, men, milk, muck, Murmur 16
net knit nook nut nerd 17 pet pit put put put pert 18 Pell pill pull pearl 19 red
red root rut rural 20 said sit sit such search 21 shed shin shut sure 22 sled slim
slug slur 23 stead still stood stuff stir 24 it's stood it stick it stood it's done
it's dirt 25 stretch string struck 26 tell tip took, ton, turn, 27, then, this, thus,
28, thing, thug, third, 29, vex, vim, thug, verb, thirty, wet, wind, wood, was,
word, thirty-one, yet, in, young, yearn, thirty-two, zen, zinfandel, result,
deserve.